Register of the Robert H. Malott letters received
Hoover Institution Archives
Robert H. Malott letters received
1971-2013
2015C28
Hoover Institution Archives
8.0 manuscript boxes (3.2 linear feet)
Letters received by Robert H. Malott, the chairman and chief executive officer of FMC Corporation, from American and foreign political, diplomatic, military and business leaders, relating to domestic and international affairs.
Malott, Robert H.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2015.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
Robert H. Malott was born in 1926, in Boston, Massachusetts. He received his Bachelor of Arts degree in 1948 from the University of Kentucky, and his Master of Business Administration degree in 1950 from the Harvard Graduate School of Business Administration. He served as the Chief Executive Officer and Chairman of the FMC Corporation from 1970-1991.
Malott served on the Boards of Amoco, United Technologies, Bell & Howell, and the Swiss Bank. He also participated on the Boards of various public policy, educational, and civic organizations, including the Hoover Institution, Argonne National Laboratories, the Aspen Institute, the Business Roundtable, the University of Chicago, the Illinois Math and Science Academy, the Chicago Botanic Garden, the Lyric Opera of Chicago, the National World War II Museum, the National Museum of National History (Smithsonian), the Public Broadcasting System, the National Park Foundation, the Chicago Symphony Orchestra, and the American Enterprise Institute.
Scope and Contents note
This collection is comprised of letters received by Malott from twentieth century American and foreign political, diplomatic, military and business leaders. The correspondence, between Malott and recipients, who include members of Congress as well as foreign diplomats, largely concerns political, business, and military matters, but also includes letters related to campaign contributions and attendance at conferences and social events. Especially notable among the correspondence are significant collections of letters sent by George H. W. Bush, Bob Dole, Richard Nixon, and Jim Edgar, relating to their political campaigns.
United States--Foreign relations.; United States--Politics and government.
- Letters received, 1971-2013
  - Correspondence Index, 2003 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Abramowitz, Morton, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Abshire, David, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Acland, Antony, 1986 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Al Saud, Fahd Ben Abdelazeez, 1975 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Aleman, Miguel, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Alfonsin, Guillermo, 1985 (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Allen, Teddy, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Al-Sabah, Saud Nasir, 1988 (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - Ambrose, James, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Ambrose, Stephen, 1999 (Box-folder 1: 11)
  - Amouzegan, Jamshid, 1977, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Anderson, John, 1978 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - Andreani, Jacques, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 14)
  - Andrus, Cecil, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 15)
  - Arens, Moshe, 1982 (Box-folder 1: 16)
  - Armacost, Michael, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 1: 17)
  - Armstrong, Anne, undated (Box-folder 1: 18)
  - Ashcroft, John, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 1: 19)
  - Askew, Reubin, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 20)
  - Aspin, Les, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 1: 21)
  - Atiyeh, Victor, 1986, 1989 (Box-folder 1: 22)
  - Azim, Ejaz, 1986 (Box-folder 1: 23)
  - Aziz, Mokren Ben Abdul, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 24)
  - Babbitt, Bruce, 1994 (Box-folder 1: 25)
  - Baker, Howard, 1979-1995 (Box-folder 1: 26)
  - Baker, James, 1980, 1985 (Box-folder 1: 27)
  - Balcerowicz, Leszek, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 28)
  - Baldridge, Malcolm, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 1: 29)
  - Baliles, Gerald, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 1: 30)
  - Ball, William, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1: 31)
  - Bangerter, Norman, 1989 (Box-folder 1: 32)
  - Bennett, Charles, 1987, 1991 (Box-folder 1: 33)
  - Bennett, W. Tapley, 1982 (Box-folder 1: 34)
  - Bentsen, Lloyd, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 1: 35)
  - Bernardin, Joseph, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 1: 36)
  - Bessmernykh, Alexander, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 37)
  - Beteta, Mario Ramon, 1983 (Box-folder 1: 38)
  - Betti, John, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 39)
  - Biden, Joseph, 1990 (Box-folder 1: 40)
  - Billington, James, 1991 (Box-folder 1: 41)
  - Bin Sultan, Bandar, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 1: 42)
  - Bingaman, Jeff, 1983 (Box-folder 1: 43)
  - Black, Shirley Temple, 1975 (Box-folder 1: 44)
  - Blinken, Alan, 1994 (Box-folder 1: 45)
  - Bond, Christopher, 1981-1996 (Box-folder 1: 46)
  - Borchgrave d'Altena, Alexandra de, 1988 (Box-folder 1: 47)
  - Boren, Mary Ellen and James, 1983 (Box-folder 1: 48)
  - Borling, John, 1991 (Box-folder 1: 49)
  - Borman, Frank, 1977 (Box-folder 1: 50)
  - Boschwitz, Rudy, 1984, 1986 (Box-folder 1: 51)
  - Boskin, Michael, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 1: 52)
  - Bower, Marvin, 1972 (Box-folder 1: 53)
  - Bradley, Bill, 1984, 1991 (Box-folder 1: 54)
  - Brady, Nicholas, 1988 (Box-folder 1: 55)
  - Brandstetter, Frank, 1971 (Box-folder 1: 56)
  - Branstad, Terry, 1988, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 57)
  - Breaux, John, undated (Box-folder 1: 58)
  - Breeden, Richard, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 59)
  - Brittan, Leon, 1991 (Box-folder 1: 60)
  - Broad, Eli, 1971 (Box-folder 1: 61)
  - Brook, William, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 1: 62)
  - Brown, Hank, 1990, 1994 (Box-folder 1: 63)
  - Broyhill, James, undated (Box-folder 1: 64)
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1978 (Box-folder 1: 65)
  - Buchanan, Patrick, 1985 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Buffet, Warren, 2010 (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - Bundy, McGeorge, 1978 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Burger, Warren, 1982 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Burkhardt, Arthur, 1988 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Burns, Arthur, 1984 (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Bush, Barbara, 1998 (Box-folder 2: 7)
  - Bush, George H. W., 1977-1998 (Box-folder 2: 8)
  - Bush, George W., 1992-1998 (Box-folder 2: 9)
  - Bush, Prescott, 1983 (Box-folder 2: 10)
  - Bustamente, Albert, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 11)
  - Byrne, Jane, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Byron, Beverly, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 13)
  - Campbell, Tom, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 2: 14)
  - Carlucci, Frank, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 2: 15)
  - Carrick, Roger, 1986, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 16)
  - Carrillo-Castro, Alejandro, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 17)
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 2: 18)
  - Carter, Powell, undated (Box-folder 2: 19)
  - Casey, Albert, 1982 (Box-folder 2: 20)
  - Casey, William, 1981 (Box-folder 2: 21)
  - Catto, Henry, 1989 (Box-folder 2: 22)
  - Celeste, Richard, 1988, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 23)
  - Chafee, John, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 24)
  - Chao, Elaine, 2001 (Box-folder 2: 25)
  - Chaozhu, Ji, 1985 (Box-folder 2: 26)
  - Cheney, Dick, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 2: 27)
  - Chien, Frederick, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 28)
  - Christopherson, Henning, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 29)
  - Clausen, A. W., 1971, 1983 (Box-folder 2: 30)
  - Clements, William, 1979 (Box-folder 2: 31)
  - Clinton, Bill, 1990, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 32)
  - Coats, Dan, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 33)
  - Cohen, William, 1989 (Box-folder 2: 34)
  - Collins, Cardiss, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 35)
  - Colon, Rafael Hernandez, 1986 (Box-folder 2: 36)
  - Compton, James, 1988 (Box-folder 2: 37)
  - Connally, John, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 2: 38)
  - Cook, Michael, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 39)
  - Craig, Larry, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 40)
  - Crandall, R. L., 1988 (Box-folder 2: 41)
  - Crane, Philip, 1995 (Box-folder 2: 42)
  - Crespo-Velasco, Jorge, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 53)
  - Crowe, William, 1988 (Box-folder 2: 44)
  - Cutler, Lloyd, 1994, 1998 (Box-folder 2: 45)
  - Daley, Richard, 1982-1998 (Box-folder 2: 46)
  - Dalrymple, Rawdon, 1988, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 47)
  - Danforth, John, 1986 (Box-folder 2: 48)
  - Daniels, Lee, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 2: 49)
  - Daoyu, Li, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 50)
  - Davis, J. B., 1991 (Box-folder 2: 51)
  - Davis, Jack, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2: 52)
  - Dawkins, Pete, 1988 (Box-folder 2: 53)
  - Day O'Connor, Sandra, 1998 (Box-folder 2: 54)
  - Demirel, Süleyman, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 55)
  - Denman, Roy, 1987 (Box-folder 2: 56)
  - Derrick, Butler, 1983 (Box-folder 2: 57)
  - Deukmejian, George, 1984, 1986 (Box-folder 2: 58)
  - Deutch, John, 1993, 1995 (Box-folder 2: 59)
  - Didrickson, Loleta, undated (Box-folder 2: 60)
  - Dingell, John, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 2: 61)
  - DiPrete, Edward, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 62)
  - Ditka, Mike, 1988 (Box-folder 2: 63)
  - Dixon, Alan, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 2: 64)
  - Dole, Bob, 1979-1995 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Dole, Elizabeth, 1983 (Box-folder 3: 2)
  - Domenici, Pete, 1989 (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Draper, William, 1982 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Duberstein, Kenneth, 1988 (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Dunne, George, 1982 (Box-folder 3: 6)
  - Du Pont, Pierre, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 3: 7)
  - Durenburger, Dave, 1986 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Eagleton, Thomas, 1985 (Box-folder 3: 9)
  - Earl, Anthony, 1983 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Edgar, Jim, 1984-1998 (Box-folder 3: 11)
  - Edson, Gary, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 12)
  - Eide, Vigleik, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 13)
  - Elekdağ, Şükrü, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 3: 14)
  - Epton, Bernard, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 3: 15)
  - Espinosa de los Reyes, Jorge, 1985 (Box-folder 3: 16)
  - Evans, Daniel, 1988 (Box-folder 3: 17)
  - King Faisal ibn Abdul Aziz al Saud, 1975 (Box-folder 3: 18)
  - Fascell, Dante, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 19)
  - Fawell, Harris, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 20)
  - Fedders, John, 1983 (Box-folder 3: 21)
  - Feldstein, Martin, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 3: 22)
  - Field, Marshall, 1984 (Box-folder 3: 23)
  - Fletcher, James, 1986 (Box-folder 3: 24)
  - Fletcher, Patricia, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 25)
  - Foley, Thomas, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 26)
  - Gavin, John, 1983 (Box-folder 3: 27)
  - Ford, Gerald, 1975-1998 (Box-folder 3: 28)
  - Ford, Henry, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 3: 29)
  - François-Poncet, Jean, 1971-1985 (Box-folder 3: 30)
  - Franklin, Barbara, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 31)
  - Franks, Gary, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 32)
  - Frenzel, Bill, 1985 (Box-folder 3: 33)
  - Fu San, Zhao, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 34)
  - Fullerton, W. H., 1991 (Box-folder 3: 35)
  - Galbraith, Evan, 1982 (Box-folder 3: 36)
  - Gelb, Bruce, undated (Box-folder 3: 37)
  - Geo-Karis, Adeline, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 38)
  - Ghorbal, Ashraf, 1977 (Box-folder 3: 39)
  - Gingrich, Newt, 1995 (Box-folder 3: 40)
  - Glenn, John, 1984, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 41)
  - Glitman, Maynard, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 42)
  - Godwin, Richard, 1987 (Box-folder 3: 43)
  - Gordon, Albert, 1971 (Box-folder 3: 44)
  - Gore, Al, 1993 (Box-folder 3: 45)
  - Gradison, Bill, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 46)
  - Graham, Bob, 1983 (Box-folder 3: 47)
  - Graham, Katharine, 1984 (Box-folder 3: 48)
  - Gramm, Phil, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 3: 49)
  - Greenspan, Alan, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 50)
  - Gregg, Donald, 1989, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 51)
  - Grunwald, Henry, 1988 (Box-folder 3: 52)
  - Gvishiani, J., 1977 (Box-folder 3: 53)
  - Hagin, Joseph, 1989 (Box-folder 3: 54)
  - Haig, Alexander, 1981-1982, 1989 (Box-folder 3: 55)
  - Hall, James, 1991 (Box-folder 3: 56)
  - Halliday, A. L., 1985 (Box-folder 3: 56)
  - Hamilton, Lee, 1987, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 3: 58)
  - Harkin, Tom, 2002 (Box-folder 3: 59)
  - Hartigan, Neil, 1984, 1987, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 60)
  - Hartman, Arthur, 1982, 1984 (Box-folder 3: 61)
  - Hastert, J. Dennis, 1991, 1999 (Box-folder 3: 62)
  - Hatch, Orrin, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 3: 63)
  - Hawke, R. J. L., 1990 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - Hawkins, Paula, 1986 (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - Hayden, Mike, 1987, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - Hearder, Jeremy, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - Hefley, Joel, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Heflin, Howell, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - Heinz, John, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - Henderson, Nicholas, 1981 (Box-folder 4: 8)
  - Herrington, John, 1987 (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - Herzog, Jesus, 1991 (Box-folder 4: 10)
  - Hewitt, William, 1984 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Hillary, Ed, 1981 (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - Hills, Carla, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - Hollings, Ernest, 1991 (Box-folder 4: 14)
  - Houghton, Amo, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - Huang, Ju, 1991 (Box-folder 4: 16)
  - Hubbard, Allan, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 17)
  - Hughes, Harry, 1986 (Box-folder 4: 18)
  - Hummel, Arthur, 1985 (Box-folder 4: 19)
  - Humphrey, Gordon, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 20)
  - Hunter, Robert, 1994 (Box-folder 4: 21)
  - King Hussein, 1976 (Box-folder 4: 22)
  - Hyde, Henry, 1991, 1995 (Box-folder 4: 23)
  - Inman, Bobby, 1993 (Box-folder 4: 24)
  - Jackson, Harry, 1978, 1981 (Box-folder 4: 25)
  - Jacobi, Klaus, 1984 (Box-folder 4: 26)
  - Jacques, Horace, 1982 (Box-folder 4: 27)
  - James, Ben, 1981 (Box-folder 4: 28)
  - Javitz, Jacob, 1980 (Box-folder 4: 29)
  - Jewkes, Gordon, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 30)
  - Johnson, Nancy, 1987 (Box-folder 4: 31)
  - Jones, James, 1982 (Box-folder 4: 32)
  - Kandemir, Nuzhet, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 4: 33)
  - Karita, Yoshio, 1986, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 34)
  - Kassebaum, Nancy, 1987 (Box-folder 4: 35)
  - Kasten, Robert, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 4: 36)
  - Kaul, P. K., 1988 (Box-folder 4: 37)
  - Keats, Roger, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 38)
  - Kelley, Paul, 1983, 1991 (Box-folder 4: 39)
  - Kemp, Jack, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 4: 40)
  - Kempthorne, Dirk, 1993 (Box-folder 4: 41)
  - Kerr, John, 1991 (Box-folder 4: 42)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1984-1990, 1993 (Box-folder 4: 43)
  - Klutznick, Philip, 1980 (Box-folder 4: 44)
  - Koppel, Ted, 1982 (Box-folder 4: 45)
  - Kořán, Jaroslav, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 46)
  - Kreps, Juanita, 1979 (Box-folder 4: 47)
  - Kumar, Anil, 1989 (Box-folder 4: 48)
  - Kustra, Bob, 1989, 1992, 1995 (Box-folder 4: 49)
  - Landers, Ann, 1982 (Box-folder 4: 50)
  - Larosiere, Jacques de, 1983 (Box-folder 4: 51)
  - Lauder, Ronald, 1986 (Box-folder 4: 52)
  - Ledeen, Leon, 1989 (Box-folder 4: 53)
  - Lehrman, Lewis, 1982, 1985 (Box-folder 4: 54)
  - Leigh, Michael, 1991 (Box-folder 4: 55)
  - Lewis, Drew, 1982-1984, 1988 (Box-folder 4: 56)
  - Li, K. T., 1991 (Box-folder 4: 57)
  - Lichenstein, Charles, 1983 (Box-folder 4: 58)
  - Lieberman, Joseph, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 4: 59)
  - Linowitz, Sol, 1980, 1985, 1989, 1998 (Box-folder 4: 60)
  - List, Robert, 1982 (Box-folder 4: 61)
  - Llado, José, 1979 (Box-folder 4: 62)
  - Loeb, John, 1983 (Box-folder 4: 63)
  - Long, R. L. J., 1983 (Box-folder 4: 64)
  - Long, Russell, 1983, 1986 (Box-folder 4: 65)
  - Lord, Winston, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 4: 66)
  - Lott, Trent, 1997 (Box-folder 4: 67)
  - Lovell, James, 1986 (Box-folder 4: 68)
  - Lowther, Clare, 1991 (Box-folder 4: 69)
  - Lugar, Richard, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 4: 70)
  - Lujan, Manuel, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 4: 71)
  - Lynch, Jack, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - Macdonald, Virginia, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - MacGregor, Ian, 1985 (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - Madigan, Edward, 1992 (Box-folder 5: 4)
  - Madigan, Michael, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - Manley, John, 1995 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - Manueco, Gabriel, 1985 (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Marentes, Pablo, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 8)
  - Marsh, John, 1986 (Box-folder 5: 9)
  - Martens, Wilfried, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 10)
  - Martin, Lynn, 1984, 1987, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 5: 11)
  - Matheson, Scott, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 12)
  - Matsui, Mitsuru, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 13)
  - Matsunaga, Nobuo, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 5: 14)
  - Maybus, Ray, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 15)
  - McCain, John, 1988 (Box-folder 5: 16)
  - McClure, Frederick, 1989 (Box-folder 5: 17)
  - McCollum, Bill, 1983 (Box-folder 5: 18)
  - McConnell, Mitch, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 19)
  - McCurdy, Dave, 1988 (Box-folder 5: 20)
  - McEwen, Bob, 1987, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 21)
  - McLaughlin, Ann, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 5: 22)
  - McVey, Peter, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 23)
  - Meana, Carlo Ripa di, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 24)
  - Meese, Edwin, 1982-1983, 1986 (Box-folder 5: 25)
  - Merrill, Philip, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 26)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1983 (Box-folder 5: 27)
  - Michel, Robert, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 5: 28)
  - Miller, Bob, 1989 (Box-folder 5: 29)
  - Miller, William, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 5: 30)
  - Mineta, Norman, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 5: 31)
  - Mingay, F. R., 1990 (Box-folder 5: 32)
  - Mitchell, George, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 33)
  - Mondale, Walter, 1976, 1977, 1992 (Box-folder 5: 34)
  - Mondéjar, Marques de, 1983 (Box-folder 3: 35)
  - Montgomery, Gillespie, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 36)
  - Moodey, James, 1986 (Box-folder 5: 37)
  - Moore, Arch, 1984 (Box-folder 5: 38)
  - Moore, John, 1983 (Box-folder 5: 39)
  - Moorer, Thomas, 1983 (Box-folder 5: 40)
  - Mosbacher, Robert, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 5: 41)
  - Moscone, George, 1977 (Box-folder 5: 42)
  - Moseley-Brown, Carol, 1994 (Box-folder 5: 43)
  - Moynihan, Daniel, 1977-1978, 1988 (Box-folder 5: 44)
  - Murdoch, Rupert, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 5: 45)
  - Murphy, Richard, 1984, 1987 (Box-folder 5: 46)
  - Nakemura, Takeshi, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 47)
  - Narich, Richard, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 48)
  - Ney, Richard, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 5: 49)
  - Nickles, Don, 1984, 1996 (Box-folder 5: 50)
  - Nicolas, Pierre, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 51)
  - Niles, Thomas, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 52)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1984, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 53)
  - North, Oliver, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 54)
  - Nunn, Sam, 1987, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 5: 55)
  - Obama, Barack, 2001 (Box-folder 5: 56)
  - Okawara, Yoshio, 1984-1985, 1993 (Box-folder 5: 57)
  - O'Malley, Jack, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box-folder 5: 58)
  - Oppenheimer, H. F., 1978 (Box-folder 5: 59)
  - Orr, Kay, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 60)
  - Orr, Robert, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 5: 61)
  - Owens, Williams, 1998 (Box-folder 5: 62)
  - Özal, Semra, undated (Box-folder 5: 63)
  - Pandolfi, Filippo, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 64)
  - Patten, Christopher, 2001 (Box-folder 5: 65)
  - Penske, Roger, 1988 (Box-folder 5: 66)
  - Percy, Charles, 1977, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 5: 67)
  - Peres, Shimon, 1977, 1980, 1986, 1993 (Box-folder 5: 68)
  - Perpich, Rudy, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 5: 69)
  - Perry, William, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 5: 70)
  - Petrignani, Rinaldo, 1982 (Box-folder 5: 71)
  - Philip, James, 1991 (Box-folder 5: 72)
  - Pickering, Thomas, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 5: 73)
  - Porter, John, 1985-1986, 1990, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Porter, Roger, 1989 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Powell, Colin, 1988-1991, 1997 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Pressler, Larry, 1984, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Price, Charles, 1982, 1985, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Pucinski, Aurelia, 1998 (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - Quayle, Dan, 1987-1992, 1996 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Ramos, Fidel, 1986, 1992 (Box-folder 6: 8)
  - Randolph, Jennings, 1985 (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Range, Rebecca, 1988 (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - Rasmussen, K. W., 1984 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1981-1983, 1985 (Box-folder 6: 12)
  - Reed, Barbara, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 13)
  - Regan, Donald, 1982 (Box-folder 6: 14)
  - Regan, Gerald, 1984 (Box-folder 6: 15)
  - Renwick, Robin, 1991 (Box-folder 6: 16)
  - Rhodes, Frank, 1996 (Box-folder 6: 17)
  - Rice, Donald, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 18)
  - Ridgway, Rozanne, 1989 (Box-folder 6: 19)
  - Riley, Richard, 1983, 1986 (Box-folder 6: 20)
  - Robb, Charles, 1990, 1994 (Box-folder 6: 21)
  - Robin, Gabriel, 1991 (Box-folder 6: 22)
  - Robinson, Paul, 1982, 1985 (Box-folder 6: 23)
  - Robson, John, 1991 (Box-folder 6: 24)
  - Rock, Philip, 1986, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 6: 25)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1998 (Box-folder 6: 26)
  - Roemer, Buddy, 1988, 1991 (Box-folder 6: 27)
  - Rostenkowski, Dan, 1982-1992 (Box-folder 6: 28)
  - Roth, William, 1987, 1989 (Box-folder 6: 29)
  - Ruder, David, 1988 (Box-folder 6: 30)
  - Rumsfeld, Donald, 1980, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 6: 31)
  - Ryan, George, 1982-1983, 1986, 1989 (Box-folder 6: 32)
  - Ryan, Jim, 1994 (Box-folder 6: 33)
  - Saavedra, Gustavo, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 34)
  - Sabo, Martin, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 35)
  - Salah, Abdullah, 1976 (Box-folder 6: 36)
  - Salgado, Joseph, 1988 (Box-folder 6: 37)
  - Sanchez-Camara, Antonio, 1991 (Box-folder 6: 38)
  - Sanford, Terry, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 39)
  - Santini, James, 1982 (Box-folder 6: 40)
  - Schaefer, Dan, 1991 (Box-folder 6: 41)
  - Schaefer, William, 1990, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 42)
  - Schaufele, William, 1980 (Box-folder 6: 43)
  - Schlesinger, James, undated (Box-folder 6: 44)
  - Schlüter, Poul, 1984 (Box-folder 6: 45)
  - Schroeder, Patricia, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 6: 46)
  - Schuette, Bill, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 47)
  - Scowcroft, Brent, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 48)
  - Shad, John, 1988 (Box-folder 6: 49)
  - Sheffield, Bill, 1984 (Box-folder 6: 50)
  - Shultz, George, 1982, 1987, 1989 (Box-folder 6: 51)
  - Silva, Alicia, 1991 (Box-folder 6: 52)
  - Silva, Patricio, 1991 (Box-folder 6: 53)
  - Silveira, Antonio Azaredo da, 1980 (Box-folder 6: 54)
  - Simon, Paul, 1985-1994 (Box-folder 6: 55)
  - Simon, Seymour, 1988 (Box-folder 6: 56)
  - Simpson, Alan, 1984-1986, 1989-1991, 1995, 2013 (Box-folder 6: 57)
  - Singh, Karan, undated (Box-folder 6: 58)
  - Sinner, George, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 59)
  - Skinner, Samuel, 1989, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 6: 60)
  - Slattery, Jim, 1988 (Box-folder 6: 61)
  - Small, Karna, 1981 (Box-folder 6: 62)
  - Smith, William, 1991 (Box-folder 6: 63)
  - Spasowski, Romuald, 1978, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 64)
  - Specter, Arlen, 1990, 1992 (Box-folder 6: 65)
  - Spero, Joan, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 66)
  - Stennis, John, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 67)
  - Stevens, Ted, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 68)
  - Stevenson, Adlai, 1983, 1985 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Stockdale Jim and Sybil, 1991-1992, 1995 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Stone, Michael, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Strauss, Robert, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 7: 4)
  - Sullivan, Mike, 1989-1990, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 7: 5)
  - Symms, Steve, 1986 (Box-folder 7: 6)
  - Szeged, Adriaan Jacobovitz, 1991 (Box-folder 7: 7)
  - Taft, William, 1991 (Box-folder 7: 8)
  - Tallon, Robin, 1984 (Box-folder 7: 9)
  - Tarr, Curtis, 1971 (Box-folder 7: 10)
  - Thayer, Paul, 1983 (Box-folder 7: 11)
  - Thomas, Craig, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 12)
  - Thomas, Lowell, 1976-1977, 1981 (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - Thompson, James, 1976-1980, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 7: 14)
  - Thompson, Tommy, 1987-1990, 1992, 1994 (Box-folder 7: 15)
  - Thornburgh, Dick, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 7: 16)
  - Thurmond, Strom, 1983, 1987, 1990, 1992 (Box-folder 7: 17)
  - Thuysbaert, P., 1991 (Box-folder 7: 18)
  - Tindemans, L., 1978 (Box-folder 7: 19)
  - Tisch, Preston, 1986 (Box-folder 7: 20)
  - Todman, Terence, 1983 (Box-folder 7: 21)
  - Totten, Donald, 1981 (Box-folder 7: 22)
  - Tower, John, 1984 (Box-folder 7: 23)
  - Trible, Paul, 1987 (Box-folder 7: 24)
  - Upton, Fred, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 25)
  - Valentine, G. D., undated (Box-folder 7: 26)
  - VanderJagt, Guy, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 27)
  - Van-Thinh, Tran, 1991 (Box-folder 7: 28)
  - Verity, C. William, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 7: 29)
  - Vernier-Palliez, Bernard, 1982 (Box-folder 7: 30)
  - Vessey, John, 1983 (Box-folder 7: 31)
  - Vest, George, 1984 (Box-folder 7: 32)
  - Voinovich, George, undated (Box-folder 7: 33)
  - Volcker, Paul, 1983 (Box-folder 7: 34)
  - Vyas, Dinesh, 1989 (Box-folder 7: 35)
  - Walker, Edward, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 36)
  - Wallop, Malcolm, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 37)
  - Walters, David, 1994 (Box-folder 7: 38)
  - Wangeman, Frank, 1971 (Box-folder 7: 39)
  - Warner, John, 1980, 1984, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 7: 40)
  - Watkins, James, 1991 (Box-folder 7: 41)